Technical University of British Columbia fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Office of the President records, 1986 - 2002; F-177-1; 8.65 m of textual records and other material; Dates of creation: Predominant dates of the series are 1995-2002. Physical description: Includes 46 photographs, 3 contact sheets, 14 videocassettes, 3 audio cassettes, 1 compact disk, and 2 artifa
  - TechBC historical files, 1988 - 2002; F-177-1-17; Analog originals 1.15 m of textual records 10 moving images (12 videocassettes) 3 sound recordings (3 audiocassettes) 2 artifacts Digitized materials: Preservation copies - 11 mov files (201.95 GB); 4 wav files (3.38 GB) Access copies - 11 mp4 fi
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: LINK file, 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-17-0-30 (Archival box - standard 177-57)
    - Participation rate, student tracking [reports]: Standing Room Only - The Case for Expanding BC's Universities, January 1998; F-177-1-17-0-31 (Archival box - standard 177-57)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 96-001: Data and Analyses Required to Support Academic Planning - Results of Phase One Development of an Electronic Factbook, 1 April 1996; F-177-1-17-0-32 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 96-002: Interim Planning Council Preliminary Report to Ministry (Draft), 3 June 1996; F-177-1-17-0-33 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 96-003: Data and Analyses Required to Support Academic Planning - Results of Phase Two Development of an Electronic Factbook, 15 May 1996; F-177-1-17-0-34 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 96-006: Annual Report of the Technical University Society of Britsh Columbia, 24 October 1996; F-177-1-17-0-35 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 96-007: Connected in a Network: TechBC - Its Students, the Labour Market, Industry and Society, November 1996; F-177-1-17-0-36 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 96-008: TechBC: Participation, Access and Capacity, 18 December 1996; F-177-1-17-0-37 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 97-009: Technical University of British Columbia: Five Priority Questions, 3 January 1997; F-177-1-17-0-38 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 97-010: Educational Technology and Learnng Complex, 24 February 1997; F-177-1-17-0-39 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 97-012: Student Services and the Student Society: A Proposal, 20 January 1997 - 3 January 1997; F-177-1-17-0-40 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 97-013: Human Resource Issues, 21 February 1997; F-177-1-17-0-41 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 97-015: Ten Points, 25 April 1997; F-177-1-17-0-42 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 97-016: Historical Review, 24 March 1997; F-177-1-17-0-43 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 97-017: Current Pedagogic Use of the Internet, April 1997; F-177-1-17-0-44 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 97-019: Space profile, July 1997; F-177-1-17-0-45 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 97-020: Computer Based Learning in Higher Education, July 1997; F-177-1-17-0-46 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - TechBC reports I - Internal Planning Report 97-021: History of the Technical University of British Columbia, 31 October 1997; F-177-1-17-0-47 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - Report: Cost per FTE, 1996; F-177-1-17-0-48 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - [Report]: Technical University of British Columbia: Student Services and the Student Society: A Proposal (Draft), 1997; F-177-1-17-0-49 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-008 (drafts), 1996; F-177-1-17-0-50 (Archival box - standard 177-58)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-007: TechBC - its Students, the Labour Market, Industry and Society (drafts), 31 October 1996; F-177-1-17-0-51 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Internal Planning Report 97-016: Historical Review (draft), 24 March 1997; F-177-1-17-0-52 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-001: Data and Analyses Required to Support Academic Planning - Results of Phase One Development of an Electronic Factbook (draft for committee review), 1 April 1996; F-177-1-17-0-53 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Internal Planning Report 96.002: Data and Analyses Required to Support Academic Planning - Results of Phase Two Development of an Electronic Factbook, 15 May 1996; F-177-1-17-0-54 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - GVRD [comments regarding location of new BC Technical University], 1995; F-177-1-17-0-55 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Report: Is It Worth Doing a Science or Technology Degree in Canada?, November 1997; F-177-1-17-0-56 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Report: Proposed Bachelor of Information Technology - Kwantlen College, March 1997; F-177-1-17-0-57 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Report: Surrey: The State of the City, July 1994; F-177-1-17-0-58 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Brochure: TechBC: A University for the New Millenium, 1998; F-177-1-17-0-59 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Report: Royal Roads University Educational Needs Survey of Advanced Technology Companies on Vancouver Island, 22 November 1996; F-177-1-17-0-60 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Report: Technical University of British Columbia: Site Classification Review, 22 January 1998; F-177-1-17-0-61 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Report: The University College in B.C.: A New Paradigm in Higher Education?, 1994; F-177-1-17-0-62 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Report: Technical University of British Columbia, Rezoning/Subdivision Process Review, Engineering Pre-Feasibility Review, June 1996; F-177-1-17-0-63 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Report: Education Plan for Royal Roads University: Our Unique Vision, 1996; F-177-1-17-0-64 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Report: The British Columbia High Technology Sector, 1988-1994, March 1996; F-177-1-17-0-65 (Archival box - standard 177-64)
    - Report: Study of the new media industry in British Columbia, October 1995; F-177-1-17-0-66 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Report: Royal Roads University Business Plan, September 1996; F-177-1-17-0-67 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Report: History of FTE's 1990/91 to 1993/94, November 1994; F-177-1-17-0-68 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Report: History of FTE's 1991/92 to 1994/95, December 1995; F-177-1-17-0-69 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-004: Demographic, Educational and Occupational Profiles of 1988 Graduates…, vol. 1, October 1996; F-177-1-17-0-70 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-005: Local Industry Needs Analysis, vol. 1, November 1996; F-177-1-17-0-71 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-006: Technical University of BC Annual Report, 1995-1996, vol. 1, F-177-1-17-0-72 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-007: Connected in a Network: TechBC - its Students, the Labour Market, Industry and Society, vol. 1, November 1996; F-177-1-17-0-73 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-008: TechBC: Participation, Access and Capacity, 18 December 1996; F-177-1-17-0-74 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Internal Planning Report 97-009: Five Priority Questions, 3 January 1997; F-177-1-17-0-75 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Internal Planning Report 97-010: Educational Technology and Learning Complex, 24 February 1997; F-177-1-17-0-76 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Internal Planning Report 97-012: Student Services and the Student Society: A Proposal, 20 January 1994; F-177-1-17-0-77 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Internal Planning Report 97-013: Human Resource Issues, 21 February 1997; F-177-1-17-0-78 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Internal Planning Report 97-016: Historical Review, 24 March 1997; F-177-1-17-0-79 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Fraser Valley Inventory for the Interim Planning Council and the Technical University of British Columbia, vol. 1, November 1995; F-177-1-17-0-80 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Fraser Valley Inventory for the Interim Planning Council and the Technical University of British Columbia, vol. 2, November 1995; F-177-1-17-0-81 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Institutional research from other universities I: Charting a New Course…(draft), [with correspondence], October 1995; F-177-1-17-0-82 (Archival box - standard 177-59)
    - Institutional research from other universities I: Charting a New Course…, March 1996; F-177-1-17-0-83 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Institutional research from other universities I: The Economic Benefits of Post-Secondary Education and Training in B.C.: An Outcomes Assessment, April 1996; F-177-1-17-0-84 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Institutional research from other universities I: Future Implementation - Education Task Force minutes, 21 April 1997 - April 1997; F-177-1-17-0-85 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Institutional research from other universities I: SFU, 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-17-0-86 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Institutional research from other universities I: Two Year Graduate Follow-up Survey of 1993 Baccalaureate Graduates from BC's Public Universities..., July 1996; F-177-1-17-0-87 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II: Demographic, Educational, and Occupational Profiles of 1988 High School Graduates within the Catchment Area..., October 1996; F-177-1-17-0-88 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II, 2-01: The Role of the University in Preparing the Labour Force, 1994; F-177-1-17-0-89 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II, 2-02: The Need for a University in the Fraser Valley: A case Study of Educators, January 1995; F-177-1-17-0-90 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II, 2-04: Technical University of British Columbia Interim Planning Council, Framework for Planning (Draft), February 1996; F-177-1-17-0-91 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II, 2-05: Program List 1995/96: B.C. Post-Secondary Institutions, October 1995; F-177-1-17-0-92 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II, 2-06: Charting a New Course... (draft), October 1995; F-177-1-17-0-93 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II, 2-08: An Open Door to Learning…, 12 December 1995; F-177-1-17-0-94 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II, 2-09: Inside Post-Secondary Education (draft), 1995; F-177-1-17-0-95 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II, 2-10: Prior Learning Assessment and Educational Reform: A Vision for Now (draft), December 1995; F-177-1-17-0-96 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II, 2-11: The Future of the Public Sector: An Overview for Opinion Leaders (draft), January 1996; F-177-1-17-0-97 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II, 2-12: Planning Framework for the Technical University of the Fraser Valley (draft), June 1995; F-177-1-17-0-98 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II, 2-13: Environmental Scan: An Overview of B.C.'s Learning, Socio-Economic and Labour Market Environment, February 1996; F-177-1-17-0-99 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Historical document II: TechBC reference library - index of files (May 1996) and library index - historical, F-177-1-17-0-100 (Archival box - standard 177-60)
    - Report: B.C. Human Resource Development Project - Report of the Steering Committee, November 1992; F-177-1-17-0-101 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - Report: International Workshop: The BC System of Innovation - A View from an Outside Observer, August 1995; F-177-1-17-0-102 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - Report: The Role of the University in Preparing the Labour Force: A Background Analysis, 1994; F-177-1-17-0-103 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - Report: BC Labour Force Development Board - Training for What?, 1995; F-177-1-17-0-104 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - Report: Applied Academics Pilot Project Final Report, August 1995; F-177-1-17-0-105 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - "First ever survey follows up on BC university grads" - MEST Press Release, 16 October 1996; F-177-1-17-0-106 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - Reports: TechB.C.'s development and launch plans… / Relevance and accessibility in a Fraser Valley setting, 1996 - 1998; F-177-1-17-0-107 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - TechBC Preliminary Program Information, [ca 1998]; F-177-1-17-0-108 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-002 (Draft)[with comments], vol. 1, 6 June 1996; F-177-1-17-0-109 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-002 (Draft)[with comments], vol. 2, 6 June 1996; F-177-1-17-0-110 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - Technical University of British Columbia newsletter, vol. 1, issue 1, August 1996; F-177-1-17-0-111 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - The University Presidents' Council of BC (TUPC) - annual report 1996, F-177-1-17-0-112 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - Report of the Fraser Valley Committee on Post-Secondary Education, Phase I, vol. 1, June 1993; F-177-1-17-0-113 (Archival box - standard 177-61)
    - TechBC Course Outlines 1999/2000 Academic Year, vol. 1, F-177-1-17-0-114 (Archival box - standard 177-62)
    - TechBC Multimedia Studies Program Advisory Committee meeting, November 12, 1998, November 1998; F-177-1-17-0-115 (Archival box - standard 177-62)
    - Report: Developing METL 100 - Educational Technology and Pedagogy, May 2000; F-177-1-17-0-116 (Archival box - standard 177-62)
    - Report: Preparing for the Future: A University in Surrey/White Rock, January 1993; F-177-1-17-0-117 (Archival box - standard 177-62)
    - Report: Limited Appraisal Report in a Summary Format on the Former Revy Home Centre…Surrey, BC, 12 May 2000; F-177-1-17-0-118 (Archival box - standard 177-62)
    - Report: Simon Fraser University Submission to the Fraser Valley Access Consultation Group, September 1990; F-177-1-17-0-119 (Archival box - standard 177-62)
    - Report: Higher Education in British Columbia: 1945-1995, June 1995; F-177-1-17-0-120 (Archival box - standard 177-62)
    - Report: Framework Document: Opening celebration, October 18, 1999, October 1999; F-177-1-17-0-121 (Archival box - standard 177-62)
    - Report: Tech BC Preliminary Facilities Program (draft), February 1999; F-177-1-17-0-122 (Archival box - standard 177-62)
    - Report: TechBC Academic Program Recommendations from Academic Planning Board, 1998; F-177-1-17-0-123 (Archival box - standard 177-62)
    - Technical University of British Columbia - certificate of incorporation under Society Act, 10 August 1995; F-177-1-17-0-124 (Archival box - standard 177-63)
    - Report: Technical University of British Columbia: Rezoning / Subdivision Process Review, Engineering Pre-feasibility Review, June 1996; F-177-1-17-0-125 (Archival box - standard 177-63)
    - Report: Access to Advanced Education and Training in British Columbia - Report of the Provincial Access Committee, September 1988; F-177-1-17-0-126 (Archival box - standard 177-63)
    - Report: Undergraduate Program Planning Document, January 2001; F-177-1-17-0-127 (Archival box - standard 177-63)
    - Brochure: Surrey City Centre: Meeting Many Goals, 1999; F-177-1-17-0-128 (Archival box - standard 177-63)
    - Report: TechBC: Academic Plan Information, Confidential Draft, 4 August 1998; F-177-1-17-0-129 (Archival box - standard 177-63)
    - Report: Surrey City Centre / TechBC: Meeting the Goals of the University, City, Region and Province, 1998; F-177-1-17-0-130 (Archival box - standard 177-63)
    - [Invitation - sign unveiling at campus site, 180th St. and Highway 10, Surrey, BC, April 16, 1996], F-177-1-17-0-131 (Archival box - standard 177-63)
    - Brochure: Technical University of British Columbia: Advanced Education for the Twenty-first Century, [ca 1998]; F-177-1-17-0-132 (Archival box - standard 177-63)
    - Past calendar information (for data input to BSS calendar), 2002; F-177-1-17-0-133 (Archival box - standard 177-63)
    - Interim Planning Council - document file, 1995; F-177-1-17-0-134 (Archival box - standard 177-63)
  - Early governance records, 1986 - 1998; F-177-1-18; 65 cm of textual records 3 photographs.
    Sub-series consists of records relating to Sheehan's participation as a member of the Interim Planning Council (IPC) and the Interim Governing Board (IGB) for TechBC. Includes reference files created by Sheehan relating to the activities of the Fraser Valley University Society. Activities, events and topics documented include the Fraser Valley University Society's role in the establishment of the University; meetings of the IPC and IGB; the development of TechBC's mission, mandate, and establishing legislation; the planning of academic programs, university governance, and facilities; budget development and acquisition of government funding; policy development; establishment of campus location; hiring of faculty; liaison with the Provincial Government, including the Ministry of Education, Skills and Training and Surrey MLAs; the CAUT boycott; public relations activities carried out on behalf of TechBC; as well as biographical and other information regarding IPC members. Records include minutes, agendas, and supporting papers; correpondence; articles and press releases; reports; budgets and financial statements; constitutions, bylaws and legislation; biographical material; and photographs.
    The arrangement was provided by the archivist.
    For other material relating to the early governance of the Technical University of British Columbia, see the finding aid to the Fraser Valley University Society fonds.
    - FVUS, vol. 1, 1986 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-69)
    - FVUS, vol. 2, 1986 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-69)
    - FVUS, vol. 3, 1986 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-69)
    - FVUS, vol. 4, 1986 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-69)
    - FVUS, vol. 5, 1986 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-69)
    - FVUS, vol. 6, 1986 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-69)
    - FVUS, vol. 7, 1986 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-69)
    - FVUS, vol. 8, 1986 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-69)
    - FVUS, vol. 9, 1986 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-69)
    - FVUS, vol. 10, 1986 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - IPC (minutes), vol. 1, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - IPC (minutes), vol. 2, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-12 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - IPC (mission statement), vol. 3, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-13 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - IPC (constitution/legislation), vol. 4, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-14 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - IPC (location), vol. 5, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-15 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - IPC (CEO/other resources/outside resources/research), vol. 6, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-16 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - IPC - Nov. 25 1996 meeting, F-177-1-18-0-17 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - Dyane Betts, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-18 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - Kate Braid, 1995 - 1998; F-177-1-18-0-19 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - Doug Jennings, vol. 1, 1996; F-177-1-18-0-20 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - Doug Jennings (photograph), vol. 2, 1996; F-177-1-18-0-21 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - Axel Meisen, 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-18-0-22 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - Colin Jones, 1998; F-177-1-18-0-23 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - Gerry Kilcup, vol. 1, 1996; F-177-1-18-0-24 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - Gerry Kilcup (photograph), vol. 2, 1996; F-177-1-18-0-25 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - Tom Simons, 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-18-0-26 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - Peter Jones, vol. 1, 1991 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-27 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - Peter Jones (photograph), vol. 2, 1991 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-28 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - IPC member profiles, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-29 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - Media releases, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-30 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - [IPC-general] 1996, F-177-1-18-0-31 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - IPC - Executive Committee [minutes and related papers], vol. 1, 1996; F-177-1-18-0-32 (Archival box - standard 177-70)
    - IPC - Executive Committee [minutes and related papers], vol. 2, 1996; F-177-1-18-0-33 (Archival box - standard 177-71)
    - Program delivery - committee [Program Planning Committee], 1996; F-177-1-18-0-34 (Archival box - standard 177-71)
    - Program planning - committee, 1996; F-177-1-18-0-35 (Archival box - standard 177-71)
    - Site development - committee, 1996; F-177-1-18-0-36 (Archival box - standard 177-71)
    - [Technical University of BC] - annual general meeting, 1996; F-177-1-18-0-37 (Archival box - standard 177-71)
    - MOEST - general, vol. 1, June 1995 - December 1997; F-177-1-18-0-38 (Archival box - standard 177-71)
    - MOEST - general, vol. 2, July 1995 - January 1997; F-177-1-18-0-39 (Archival box - standard 177-71)
    - IGB (minutes), vol. 1, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-18-0-40 (Archival box - standard 177-71)
    - IGB (minutes), vol. 2, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-18-0-41 (Archival box - standard 177-71)
    - IGB (minutes), vol. 3, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-18-0-42 (Archival box - standard 177-71)
    - IGB (minutes), vol. 4, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-18-0-43 (Archival box - standard 177-71)
    - IGB (minutes), vol. 5, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-18-0-44 (Archival box - standard 177-72)
    - IGB (policies, MOEST), vol. 6, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-18-0-45 (Archival box - standard 177-72)
    - IGB (legal/general), vol. 7, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-18-0-46 (Archival box - standard 177-72)
    - IGB (constitution and bylaws/budget/internal planning reports), vol. 8, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-18-0-47 (Archival box - standard 177-72)
    - IGB - members - board, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-18-0-48 (Archival box - standard 177-72)
    - [IGB - general], 1996; F-177-1-18-0-49 (Archival box - standard 177-72)
    - Annual general meeting - [Technical University Society of BC/IGB], 1997; F-177-1-18-0-50 (Archival box - standard 177-72)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], June 20, 1997, F-177-1-18-0-51 (Archival box - standard 177-72)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], May 26, 1997, F-177-1-18-0-52 (Archival box - standard 177-72)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], May 13, 1997, vol. 1, F-177-1-18-0-53 (Archival box - standard 177-72)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], May 13, 1997, vol. 2, F-177-1-18-0-54 (Archival box - standard 177-72)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], March 26, 1997, F-177-1-18-0-55 (Archival box - standard 177-73)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], March 5, 1997, vol. 1, F-177-1-18-0-56 (Archival box - standard 177-73)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], March 5, 1997, vol. 2, F-177-1-18-0-57 (Archival box - standard 177-73)